[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6079f783f0fdd9bf70464f03"
  },
  "question": "The first Saudi league was in the year __",
  "choose1": "1967",
  "choose2": "1970",
  "correct": "1976"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6079f86bf0fdd9bf70464f04"
  },
  "choose1": "Al-Ahli ",
  "choose2": "Al-Ittihad FC",
  "correct": "Al-Nassr",
  "question": "Who is the first to achieve the Saudi league?"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6079fa9bf0fdd9bf70464f05"
  },
  "choose1": "15 ",
  "choose2": "14 ",
  "correct": "16 ",
  "question": "How many teams were in the Saudi League?"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6079fbb5f0fdd9bf70464f06"
  },
  "choose1": "Al-Nassr 0:1",
  "choose2": "Al Shabab 0:1",
  "correct": "1:1 Draw",
  "question": "Who won the first match in the history of the league?"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "607a007df0fdd9bf70464f07"
  },
  "choose1": " 31 Rounds",
  "choose2": " 35 Rounds ",
  "correct": " 30 Rounds ",
  "question": "How many rounds in the Sauid league?"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "607a0248f0fdd9bf70464f08"
  },
  "choose1": "Zain Saudi Professional League",
  "choose2": "Prince Mohammed bin Salman Cup League",
  "correct": "Saudi Professional League",
  "question": "What is the seventh name of the Saudi League?"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "607a0460f0fdd9bf70464f09"
  },
  "choose1": "Hajer",
  "choose2": "Al-ansar",
  "correct": "Al-hazem",
  "question": " Team __ achieved the lowest points between 2010-2020. "
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "607a091df0fdd9bf70464f0a"
  },
  "choose1": "Leandre Tawamba",
  "choose2": "Baf√©timbi Gomis",
  "correct": " abderrazak Hamdallah",
  "question": "Who is the top scorer in 2019"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "607a0cd8f0fdd9bf70464f0b"
  },
  "choose1": "12",
  "choose2": "16 ",
  "correct": "24 ",
  "question": "The first Saudi women's league included __ teams"
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "607a0e65f0fdd9bf70464f0c"
  },
  "choose1": "Season 6",
  "choose2": "Season 4",
  "correct": "Season 3",
  "question": "In which season were professional players allowed to join the Saudi League?"
}]